Contact

rjones2114@gmail.com 229-805-0502 (Mobile) rjones2114@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rebeccajones-7983b037 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Patient Safety
Quality Patient Care

Rebecca Jones

Registered Nurse

Macon, Georgia Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Emergency Nursing, Clinical Informatics, Patient Safety, Nursing Education, Medical-Surgical Nursing, Orthopedic Nursing and Medication Administration. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (BS) focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Georgia Southwestern State University.

Experience

Navicent Health 5 years 4 months

Registered Nurse- Emergency Center February 2018 - May 2019 (1 year 4 months) Macon, Georgia

System Analyst Department of Clinical Informatics, BSN July 2017 - February 2018 (8 months)

Macon, Georgia

Registered Nurse- Emergency Center February 2014 - July 2017 (3 years 6 months) Macon, Georgia

Self Employed Registered Nurse April 2013 - February 2014 (11 months)

Caregiver: Geriatrics/Alzheimer's Disease

Manatee Memorial Hospital Registered Nurse November 2013 - January 2014 (3 months) Bradenton, Florida

ER Nursing

Aya Healthcare
Travel Nurse- RN
November 2012 - March 2013 (5 months)
Fort Defiance, Arizona

ER Nursing

Houston Healthcare
Assistant Nurse Director
September 2011 - October 2012 (1 year 2 months)
Perry, Georgia

ER/ICU

Medical Center of Central Georgia
7 years 4 months

RN-Patient Safety Coordinator
July 2009 - September 2011 (2 years 3 months)
Macon, Georgia

RN-Clinical Nurse Educator June 2006 - July 2009 (3 years 2 months) Macon, Georgia

Registered Nurse- Orthopedics June 2004 - June 2006 (2 years 1 month) Macon, Georgia

Education

Georgia Southwestern State University
Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (1999 - 2004)